

ADRI TELLEZ DIGITAL DESIGNER

I'm a graphic designer oriented to illustration and web and mobile product design. I like to create enjoyable and functional experiences, in some cases I like to use illustration as a graphic resource. I can contribute not only in design but also in templating process of a website. As well, social media design and photo retouching, etc.

EDUCATION

INSTITUTION

CUN (Corporación Unificada Nacional)

DEGREE: PROFESSIONAL TECHNICIAN IN GRAPHIC DESIGN

COURSES:

UX/UI Design

Coderhouse

After effects - Character animation

Microanimations

Domestika

Introdution to responsive web development with HTML and CSS

Domestika

Advanced web development techniques

HTML5 and CSS3

Domestika

WORK EXPERIENCE

2017 - PRESENT Freelance Designer

At El Pixel and Ego Agency.

Contributed in the UI design process for Santander Rio app.

UI design in Juegos de la Juventud legacy website.

2016 - 2017 Web/Digital Designer

Socialive Argentina

Landing pages, microsites, apps, and social media design.

2015-2016 Independent Freelance Web/Digital Designer

Participated in several clients projects, wich involved web design, illustration, editorial design and packaging design.

2010 - 2015 Graphic Designer

I worked in digital print and offset art, proffesional printer operations, as well as print and cut plotter, photographic retouch and layouting.

2009 -2010 Internship

SKILLS AND **KNOWLEDGES**

ILUSTRATOR PHOTOSHOP INDESIGN AFTER EFFECTS PREMIER SKETCH HTML5 CSS3 ACCESIBILITY USABILITY CARD SORTING STYLE GUIDE MOBILE FIRST USERFLOW DESIGN PATTERNS UX/UI DESIGN MARVEL APP

GRAPHIC TOOLS









WEB TOOLS





UX/UI TOOLS







Operative systems: Windows, OSX.

Languages:

Spanish: Native

English: Intemediate

Soldado de la Independencia 1241 CABA - Argentina



adri077@gmail.com



